[{"id":"LLrMTf_cy","serial":"1","question":"whats your father name","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","answer":"option_d","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas"},{"id":"bnGKntoiG","serial":"1","question":"whats your father name","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","answer":"option_d","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas"},{"id":"Bqp2TO_OG","serial":"1","question":"whats your father name","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","answer":"option_d","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas"},{"id":"NMo8P_yzd","serial":"1","question":"whats your father name","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","answer":"option_d","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas"},{"id":"bSTSoJvXI","serial":"1","question":"whats your father name","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","answer":"option_d","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas"},{"id":"UitX0_i5p","serial":"1","question":"whats your father name","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","answer":"option_d","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas"},{"id":"VhsP1np-g","serial":"1","question":"whats your father name","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","answer":"option_d","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas"},{"id":"iiWJcGYue","serial":"1","question":"whats your father name","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","answer":"option_d","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas"},{"id":"322LEtlTi","serial":"1","question":"whats your father name","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","answer":"option_d","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas"},{"id":"u186WQytk","serial":"1","question":"whats your father name","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","answer":"option_d","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas"},{"id":"KqZ_84GyS","serial":"1","question":"whats your father name","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","answer":"option_d","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas"},{"id":"xBbsnwmb5","serial":"1","question":"whats your father name","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","answer":"option_d","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas"},{"id":"zT3iXihDr","serial":"1","question":"whats your father name","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","answer":"option_d","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas"},{"id":"EJoJeVBoZ","serial":"1","question":"whats your father name","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","answer":"option_d","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas"},{"id":"Kwrjok3gR","serial":"1","question":"whats your father name","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","answer":"option_d","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas"},{"id":"S4ruEANT2","serial":"1","question":"whats your father name","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","answer":"option_d","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas"},{"id":"iraqwykOd","serial":"1","question":"whats your father name","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","answer":"option_d","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas"}]